For Harry and Lloyd, every day is a no-brainer.
Dumb and Dumber is a comedy film directed by Peter Farrelly.
Lloyd and Harry are two men whose stupidity is really indescribable.
When Mary, a beautiful woman, loses an important suitcase with money before she leaves for
Aspen, the two friends (who have found the suitcase) decide to return it to her.
After some "adventures" they finally get to Aspen where, using the
lost money they live it up and fight for Mary's heart.
Lloyd Christmas, played by Jim Carrey.
Harry Dunne, played by Jeff Daniels.
Mary Swanson, played by Lauren Holly.
Helen Swanson, played by Teri Garr.
Nicholas Andre, played by Charles Rocket.
J.P. Shay, played by Karen Duffy.
Dumb and Dumber To is a 2014 American buddy comedy film produced,
co-written and directed by the Farrelly brothers.
It is the third film in the Dumb and Dumber franchise, and
serves as a sequel to the 1994 film Dumb and Dumber.
The film stars Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels as Lloyd Christmas and Harry Dunne, reprising their respective roles 20 years after the events of the first film, and follows the duo as
they discover Harry has a daughter, who was set up for adoption as a baby by her single mother, leading them to journey on a cross-country road trip to locate her.
First announced in October 2011, Dumb and Dumber To underwent a turbulent pre-production phase
which included, at one point, Carrey withdrawing from the project, and Warner Bros.
Pictures exiting the project; Warner Bros.'s New Line Cinema division received
"in association with" credit, per their participation stake.
The project was eventually taken on in 2013 by Red Granite
Pictures and the film was shot later that year.
Released on November 14, 2014, by Universal Pictures, the
film received negative reviews from critics.
It grossed $36.1 million on its opening weekend and over $169 million worldwide.
On June 15, 2017, the United States Department of Justice charged that money used to
produce the film was stolen from a Malaysian government investment fund.
Red Granite Pictures denied knowingly accepting stolen money.
Prosecutors also filed a Forfeiture Complaint in federal court to seize the rights of
ownership to Dumb and Dumber To as well as the rights to the 2015 film Daddy's Home.
Red Granite later made a $60 million settlement.
The film explores themes of gas station, utah, motel, stupidity, cigar smoking.
The tone is lighthearted.